Capital Defender Office; Records apap309
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Capital Defender Case Files, 1996-2003; 2; 33.63 cubic ft.
  - McCoy Record, 1998-2000; 2.3; 6.56 cubic ft.
    The record on appeal for McCoy v. State of New York, volumes 1-32.
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 1, 1998 November 13 - 2000 September 12 (Oversized 16)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 2, 1999 March 16 - April 29 (Oversized 17)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 3, 1999 March 16 - 2000 January 14 (Oversized 17)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 4, 2000 January 18 - March 20 (Oversized 17)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 5, 2000 April 27 - August 14 (Oversized 17)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 6, 1999 March 18 - 2000 August 14 (Oversized 18)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 7, 1998 November 18 - 1999 October 13 (Oversized 18)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 8, 1999 October 14 - 2000 March 13 (Oversized 18)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 9, 2000 March 20 - March 23 (Box 1 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Folder 1)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 10, 2000 April 10 (Oversized 18)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 11, 2000 April 11 (Oversized 19)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 12, 2000 April 12 - April 13 (Oversized 19)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 13, 2000 April 17 - April 24 (Oversized 19)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 14, 2000 April 25 - April 26 (Oversized 19)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 15, 2000 April 27 - May 1 (Oversized 20)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 16, 2000 May 1 - May 2 (Oversized 20)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 17, 2000 May 3 - May 8 (Oversized 20)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 18, 2000 May 9 - May 15 (Oversized 20)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 19, 2000 May 16 - May 22 (Oversized 21)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 20, 2000 May 23 - May 24 (Oversized 21)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 21, 2000 May 25 - May 30 (Oversized 21)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 22, 2000 June 1 - June 5 (Oversized 21)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 23, 2000 June 6 - June 13 (Oversized 22)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 24, 2000 June 14 - June 19 (Oversized 22)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 25, 2000 June 20 - June 21 (Oversized 22)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 26, 2000 June 22 - June 27 (Oversized 22)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 27, 2000 June 28 - July 5 (Oversized 23)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 28, 2000 July 6 - July 11 (Oversized 23)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 29, 2000 July 11 - July 13 (Oversized 23)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 30, 2000 July 17 - July 18 (Oversized 23)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 31, 2000 July 19 - July 25 (Oversized 24)
    - McCoy v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 32, 2000 July 27 - August 7 (Oversized 24)
  - Taylor Record, 2000-2002; 2.4; 8.05 cubic ft.
    The record on appeal for Taylor v. State of New York, volumes 1-49.
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 1, 2000 May 27 - 2003 February 5 (Oversized 24, Item 1)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 2, 2000 September 15 - October 30 (Oversized 24)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 3, 2000 October 30 - December 11 (Oversized 25)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 4, 2000 December 11 - 2002 November 26 (Oversized 25)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 5, 2001 July 23 - August 17 (Oversized 25)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 6, 2001 August 17 (Oversized 25)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 7, 2001 August 17 - 2002 January 8 (Oversized 26)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 8, 2002 January 18 - February 4 (Oversized 26)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 9, 2002 February 4 - April 9 (Oversized 26)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 10, 2002 April 9 - October 17 (Oversized 26)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 11, 2002 October 24 - 2003 February 5 (Oversized 27)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 12, 2000 September 8 - 2001 September 28 (Oversized 27)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 13, 2000 September 15 - 2001 September 28 (Box 1 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 14, 2002 July 19 (Oversized 27)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 15, 2002 July 19 (Box 1 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 16, 2002 July 19 (Oversized 27)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 17, 2002 July 19 - September 19 (Oversized 28)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 18, 2000 July 27 - 2001 September 5 (Oversized 28)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 19, 2001 September 20 - November 7 (Box 1 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Item 3)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 20, 2001 November 8 - November 14 (Oversized 28)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 21, 2001 November 27 - December 10 (Oversized 28)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 22, 2001 December 11 - 2002 January 17 (Oversized 29)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 23, 2002 January 24 - April 10 (Oversized 29)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 24, 2002 April 24 - September 6 (Oversized 29)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 25, 2002 September 10 - September 13 (Box 1 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 26, 2002 September 17 - September 18 (Box 1 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 27, 2002 September 23 (Box 2 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Item 1)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 28, 2002 September 23 (Box 2 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Item 2)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 29, 2002 September 25 - September 26 (Oversized 29)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 30, 2002 September 27 - September 30 (Oversized 30)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 31, 2002 October 1 (Box 2 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Item 3)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 32, 2002 October 2 (Box 2 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Item 4)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 33, 2002 October 3 - October 4 (Oversized 30)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 34, 2002 October 15 - October 16 (Oversized 30)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 35, 2002 October 17 - October 18 (Oversized 30)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 36, 2002 October 21 - October 22 (Box 2 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 37, 2002 October 23 - October 24 (Oversized 31)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 38, 2002 October 28 - October 30 (Oversized 31)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 39, 2002 October 31 - November 1 (Oversized 31)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 40, 2002 November 4 - November 6 (Oversized 31)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 41, 2002 November 7 - November 12 (Oversized 32)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 42, 2002 November 13 - November 18 (Oversized 32)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 43, 2002 November 19 - November 22 (Oversized 32)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 45, 2000 - 2001 (Oversized 32)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 46, Undated (Oversized 33)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 47, Undated (Oversized 33)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 48, 2002 November 18 - November 25 (Box 3 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Taylor v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 49, 2000 May 28 - 2005 February 16 (Oversized 33)
  - Harris Record, 1996-1998; 2.5; 3.43 cubic ft.
    The record on appeal for Harris v. State of New York, volumes 1-4, 14-17, and 26-30. Many volumes for this case were not donated.
    - Harris v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 1, 1996 December 21 - 1998 August 18 (Oversized 33)
    - Harris v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 2, 1997 October 7 - 1998 January 21 (Oversized 34)
    - Harris v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 3, 1997 December 15 - 1998 April 21 (Oversized 34)
    - Harris v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 4, 1998 April 20 - June 29 (Oversized 34)
    - Harris v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 14, 1996 December 21 - 1998 February 13 (Oversized 34)
    - Harris v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 15, 1998 March 3 - March 16 (Oversized 35)
    - Harris v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 16, 1998 March 17 - March 18 (Oversized 35)
    - Harris v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 17, 1998 March 19 - March 23 (Oversized 35)
    - Harris v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 26, 1998 April 24 - May 4 (Oversized 35)
    - Harris v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 27, 1998 May 5 - May 8 (Oversized 36)
    - Harris v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 28, 1998 May 12 - May 15 (Oversized 36)
    - Harris v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 29, 1998 May 18 - June 2 (Oversized 36)
    - Harris v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 30, 1998 June 3 - 1999 June 10 (Oversized 36)
    - Harris v. State of New York Reply Brief for Defendant-Appelant, Undated (Oversized 37)
  - Cahill Record, 1998-1999; 2.6; 3.83 cubic ft.
    The record on appeal for Cahill v. State of New York, volumes 1-18.
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 1, 1998 April 21-1999 November 2 (Oversized 37)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 2, 1999 March 18 - April 5 (Oversized 37)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 3, 1999 April 5 - June 30 (Oversized 37)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 4, 1999 July 12 - August 16 (Oversized 38)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 5, 1999 August 17 - October 4 (Oversized 38)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 6, 1999 July 19 - July 27 (Oversized 38)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 7, 1998 June 16 - 1999 April 15 (Oversized 38)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 8, 1999 May 30 - July 30 (Oversized 39)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 9, 1999 June 13 - July 2 (Oversized 39)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 10, 1999 July 6 - July 7 (Oversized 39)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 11, 1999 July 8 - July 12 (Oversized 39)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 12, 1999 July 12 - July 13 (Oversized 40)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 13, 1999 July 19 - July 27 (Oversized 40)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 14, 1999 August 2 - August 4 (Oversized 40)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 15, 1999 August 5 - August 10 (Oversized 40)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 16, 1999 August 17 - October 5 (Oversized 41)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 17, Undated (Oversized 41)
    - Cahill v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 18, Undated (Box 1 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Folder 1)
- Death Row Conditions, 1994-2005; 3; 1.4 cubic ft.
  Death Row Conditions are mostly government studies and research of death row life for inmates. Different state standards for death row conditions are represented here.
  - Alabama DOC Information, 1998 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 1)
  - Arizona Doc Visitation Information, 2000 August 31 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 2)
  - Arkansas DOC Death Information, 1997-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 3)
  - Bound Publications from Human Rights Watch Regarding Death Row, 1997-1999 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 4)
  - California DOC Death Row Information, 1998-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 5)
  - Colorado DOC Death Row Information, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 6)
  - Connecticut Doc Death Row Information, 1997-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and Life on Death Row Article, 2001-February-02 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence regarding conditions on Death Row Nationally, 1993-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 9)
  - Death Row Policy and Associated Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 10)
  - Death Row Exonerations 1. Introduction and Explanation, 2005 May (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 11)
  - Death Row Exonerations 2. Appendix with case list and charts, 2005 May (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 12)
  - Death Row Exonerations 3. Cases, 2005 May (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 13)
  - Death Row Exonerations 4. DPIC List, 2005 May (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 14)
  - Death Row Exonerations 5. DPIC Cases of Probable Innocence, 2005 May (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 15)
  - Death Row Exonerations 6. DPIC Case Descriptions, 2005 May (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 16)
  - Death Row Exonerations 7. DPIC Report on Innocence, 2005 May (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 17)
  - Death Row Exonerations 8. "Miscarriages of Justice in Potetntially Capital Cases", 2005 May (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 18)
  - Death Row Exonerations 9. "Protecting the Innocent: A Response to the Bedau - Radelet Study" (1987), 2005 May (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 19)
  - Death Row Exonerations 10. "The Myth of Infallibility: A Reply to the Markman and Casell" (1988), 2005 May (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 20)
  - Death Row Exonerations 11. Prisoners Released from Death Row Since 1970 Because of Doubts About Their Guilt" (1996), 2005 May (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 21)
  - Death Row Exonerations 12. U.S. v. Quinoes, et al., 2005 May (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 22)
  - Death Row Exonerations 13. "Critque of DPIC List (Innocence)" (2002), 2005 May (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 23)
  - Death Row Exonerations 14. "Exonerations in the United States, 1989 through 2003" (2004), 2005 May (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 24)
  - DOCS Correspodence and Meeting Notes, 1999-2001 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 25)
  - DOCS Correspodence and Meeting Notes, 1999-2001 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 26)
  - DOCS Family Reunion Program, 2001 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 27)
  - Deleware DOC Death Row Information, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 28)
  - Florida DOC Death Row Information, Undated (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 29)
  - Georgia DOC Death Row Information, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 30)
  - Idaho DOC Death Row Information, 1997-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 31)
  - Illinois DOC Death Row Information, 1997-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 32)
  - Indiana Death Row Information, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 33)
  - Kansas DOC Death Row Information, 1998 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 34)
  - Kentucky DOC Death Row Information, 1997-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 35)
  - Louisiana DOC Death Row Information, 1998-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 36)
  - Maryland DOC Death Row Information, Undated (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 37)
  - Mississippi DOC Death Row Information, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 38)
  - Missouri DOC Death Row Information, 1998-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 39)
  - Montana DOC Death Row Information, 1999 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 40)
  - Nebraska DOC Death Row Information, 1998-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 41)
  - Nevada DOC Death Row Information, 1994-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 42)
  - New Hampshire DOC Death Row Information, 1998-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 43)
  - New Jersey DOC Death Row Information, 1998-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 44)
  - New Mexico DOC Death Row Information, 1995-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 45)
  - New York DOC Death Row Information, 1998-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 46)
  - North Carolina DOC Death Row Information, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 47)
  - Ohio DOC Death Row Information, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 48)
  - Oklahoma DOC Death Row Information, 1994-2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 49)
  - Oregon DOC Death Row Information, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 50)
  - Pennsylvania DOC Death Row Information, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 51)
  - Prisoner's Legal Service Unsorted Death Row Conditions Material (1 of 2), 1989-1999 (Box 1 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 52)
  - Prisoner's Legal Service Unsorted Death Row Conditions Material (2 of 2), 1989-1999 (Box 2 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 1)
  - Publications regarding life and Treatment on Death Row, 1994-1999 (Box 2 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 2)
  - South Carolina DOC Death Row Information, 1998-2000 (Box 2 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 3)
  - South Dakota DOC Death Row Information, 1997-2000 (Box 2 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 4)
  - Tennessee DOC Death Row Information, 1998-2000 (Box 2 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 5)
  - Texas DOC Death Row Information, 1997-2000 (Box 2 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 6)
  - Unit for Condemned Persons Reagulation of NYS DOCS, 1998-2002 (Box 2 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 7)
  - Utah DOC Death Row Information, 1998-2000 (Box 2 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 8)
  - Virginia DOC Death Row Information, 2000 (Box 2 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 9)
  - Washington Doc Death Row Information, 1997-2000 (Box 2 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 10)
  - Wyoming DOC Death Row Information, 1990-2000 (Box 2 (3-Death Row Conditions), Folder 11)
- Murder Two Indictments, 1995-2007; 4; 2.4 cubic ft.
  New York county court papers arranged by county of Murder Two indictments.
  - Albany County Murder Indictments, 1995-2005 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 1)
  - Bronx County Murder Indictments (1 of 5), 1995-2005 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 2)
  - Bronx County Murder Indictments (2 of 5), 1995-2005 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 3)
  - Bronx County Murder Indictments (3 of 5), 1995-2005 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 4)
  - Bronx County Murder Indictments (4 of 5), 1995-2005 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 5)
  - Bronx County Murder Indictments (5 of 5), 1995-2005 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 6)
  - Broome County Murder Indictments, 1999-2002 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 7)
  - Cayuga County Murder Indictments, 2002 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 8)
  - Chautauqua County Murder Indictments, 1997-2006 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 9)
  - Chemung County Murder Indictments, 1998-2006 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 10)
  - Chenango Murder Indictments, 2001-2007 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 11)
  - Clinton County Indictments, 1996-2007 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 12)
  - Columbia County Murder Indictments, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 13)
  - Cortland County Murder Indictments, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 14)
  - Dutchess County Murder Indictments, 1996-2007 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 15)
  - Erie County Murder Indictments, 1996-2006 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 16)
  - Esssex County Murder Indictments, 1997-2001 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 17)
  - Franklin County Murder Indictments, 1999-2005 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 18)
  - Fulton County Murder Indictments, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 19)
  - Genessee County Murder Indictments, 2005 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 20)
  - Greene County Murder Indictments, 2000-2004 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 21)
  - Jefferson County Murder Indictments, 1998-2005 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 22)
  - Kings County Murder Indictments (1 of 6), 1996-2007 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 23)
  - Kings County Murder Indictments (2 of 6), 1996-2007 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 24)
  - Kings County Murder Indictments (3 of 6), 1996-2007 (Box 1 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 25)
  - Kings County Murder Indictments (4 of 6), 1996-2006 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 1)
  - Kings County Murder Indictments (5 of 6), 1996-2006 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 2)
  - Kings County Murder Indictments (6 of 6), 1996-2006 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 3)
  - Monroe County Murder Indictments (1 of 2), 1995-2006 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 4)
  - Monroe County Murder Indictments (2 of 2), 1995-2006 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 5)
  - Nassau County Murder Indictments, 1996-2007 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 6)
  - New York County Murder Indictments (1 of 3), 1995-2007 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 7)
  - New York County Murder Indictments (2 of 3), 1995-2007 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 8)
  - New York County Murder Indictments (3 of 3), 1995-2007 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 9)
  - Oneida County Murder Indictments, 1996-2003 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 10)
  - Onondaga County Murder Indictments, 1995-2005 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 11)
  - Ontario County Murder Indictments, 2005 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 12)
  - Orange County Murder Indictments, 1997-2006 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 13)
  - Oswego County Murder Indictments, 2003-2005 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 14)
  - Otsego County Murder Indictments, 1996-2000 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 15)
  - Queens County Murder Indictments (1 of 3), 1997-2006 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 16)
  - Queens County Murder Indictments (2 of 3), 1997-2006 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 17)
  - Queens County Murder Indictments (3 of 3), 1997-2006 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 18)
  - Rensselaer County Murder Indictments, 1997-2003 (Box 2 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 19)
  - Richmond County Murder Indictments, 1996-2003 (Box 3 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 1)
  - Rockland County Murder Indictments, 1996-2005 (Box 3 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 2)
  - Schenectady Murder Indictments, 1995-2006 (Box 3 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 3)
  - Schoharie County Murder Indictments, 1997 (Box 3 (4-Murder Two Indictments), Folder 4)